So today I am here to solve your million dollar
question. Many people
ask that the issue of health insurance policy is
easy. It means politicians are not
a problem. Trust is established and the policy is obtained.
Issues arise at the time of Wikileaks.
Problems arise from here onwards.
So 14% of the people say that issues arise at the time of claim. It is
not smooth and
cannot be achieved.
What is that thing which you will do and
keep in mind, then your claim process will become
very smooth. So before
starting, the video file is ms * Quite a few
MS Word financial planners and
schedules with the company for the last 15 years and in the
same way, I bring you these videos in
which I solve your insurance bank key and
insurance key. So let's go to the
video. Today we will talk about
file thing to remember to have a
smooth claim settlement speed. So this
point is  I am going to discuss this point, it is
not that it is new or you people are
not aware of it or you might be hearing this for the first time, then
all these points
are well documented in the policy document for taking care of your policy, if you open the observation and
see, read your policy details, you get
your policy bond,
after that you will investigate the return, then all this
is there, we do
not open the policy and when the policy comes, we keep it and it remains lying there, when
it comes, we
open the policy bond at the same time and if it is needed, then we will
discuss what is the thing that you have to keep
in mind so that your claim
settlement can be smooth, so the first point is
that the minimum hospitalization which is required
in the health insurance policy is
not fulfilled, the target of 24-8-2018 is not met, if you go for
massage or any OPD, then it will ask for tetanus
injection, or if you
go for any observation challenge emergency, if
only OPD procedure is done, then that
insurance will not give your claim, in that it is
mandatory that you will get 24 hours  It is
necessary to stay in the hospital till then. There are some procedures
for which there is no combination of 2008, it is
not followed. See, procedures are
related to you, there is a stage
that some treatment should be done, there should be
surgery, which comes under day care,
so okay, because of your science and
hearing, because of technological advancement, the things
for which
hospitalization was required earlier, today they
go in the morning and are gone in the evening, so after
seeing those things, I will come, otherwise
hospitalization is necessary for Bigg Boss, if we
keep this in mind then there will be no music, the
second point is there is a limit, there are some
famous things on this and there is a limit on some things
in the college, that is
mentioned in your policy document, it is very
common, what is room rent,
in many polythene there is room rent cutting or there is
honey room or single private, that is why there is
no typing, where
suppose there is honey room and you thought that
I will take a higher category, then
in that case you updated your enemies, so I
am single, you thought that maybe whatever  There
is a difference in the room rent, the
insurance company will add that and will pay the rest to you,
but this does not happen, whenever you
update the rules, all the expenses get
updated, prostate all these
expenses increase, so the insurance
company does not add only the difference in your rent, if there is any other time for
arrival or
exit, then
you will have to pay approximately Rs. 2230 per room.
If you update, it is better to understand
before taking any decision. Check with the insurance
company or your policy contract
which room category
is available and even if you are going in a high-rise accommodation,
you may have to pay a prepaid extra bill payment.
If you are aware, then it will
not be a disappointment. The
third point to keep in mind at the last moment is
about waiting tickets. Whenever you
take a health insurance policy, understand
that constipation does not happen due to consumption of everything. There are some issues in
between, so the
waiting tickets are called side setting
close, specific tuition.  It happens
which is not covered for two years, it was 24th March, it will
not be covered, there will be 30 people till you take the policy, yes it happens,
I to name a few
cases replacement, so all these things will
not be covered for 2 years, if you fill in the details of these things then it will be an
optional subject
because it is clearly written in your policy that there will be
no coverage for a year, the
main point is that you need to wait, it is
important for you to know that
Tata Institute has activated the
policy, there is a meeting point on this, the second
main point is that the
waiting period for pre-existing male nurse is 3 to 4 years, it will
vary in different companies, so if
you already have a pre-existing
problem, for which you are taking medicine,
treatment of something is going on, then that
insurance will not cover you for 3 years or
for four years, if there is any hospitalization related to that then there will be
no coverage, Manager Roy, where I
would like to search here that in the pre-existing
balance, people generally take it lightly, so
What are the chances of claim rejection? The
insurance contract is based
on good faith. There is a
service principle of good faith between you and all the insurance companies that whatever
you have said is right. We have
accepted that whatever you are saying is correct. So, for that
you should be very careful while
filling and printing recently.
We take it very
lightly that it will not make much difference. The
policy will automatically cover you for 14 years.
This does not happen. Azhar application
form is for you in any other case.
This application is in front of you.
Kot Roy is thrilling. Do not take it lightly. No
matter what has always been done, do not do it in a
mathematician. Otherwise, you will not get a call.
This wait and destroys everything and does not agree with the
policy. The festival display
setting will only start in it. The policy will
not be clear. The real intention can be found. So, I am
giving you as an example,
suppose someone already had hypertension,
he did not feel it
in the policy and during the last year, a lot of other things were included, due to
which there was no direct relation with hypertension, it was
not with BT, but  He did
not appear, he would have done it but it did
not happen on beauty related legs because the
secondary and material factors which needs to be
destroyed and the policy at that time the
underwriter who is defining the politician, it is
possible that their relationship changes, if
you see the polythene wearing it, then
it is material site, whether it is
related or unrelated hospitalization, it will
not be clear, then you will have to sign, so it is
better to make it a little life
and correct the property and properly then give
two
peppermint on this policy, then
you will not be disappointed anywhere,
I am repeatedly making this point
because people complain that they did not get their claim, actually
now all the times it happens
that the claim is such that it is
not received, that the electricity bill is not a claim, if
you deposit money for the pedicure public within 2 years, then
we will not give that person insurance, so your
Avengers are necessary so that you do
not get disappointed, one point  If you have
any co-
payment or white pepper or any
explosions in it, then when you know about the co-
payment scope, send a message to these eyes that
when I will take the exam, because while getting the road
construction work insured,
there is an option of zero depression and without zero
depression, if we get the cabinet
plate done, then suppose we have taken an
insurance policy without zero
depression, then what will happen in it, if any
claim comes, then
we will have to pay 35% from our pocket and the
insurance will pay 65-70% because this production
is not included, we have to clear the cost of depression,
hence similarly, co-
payment is not there in health insurance
and for some percentage,
I will make 20% co-payment in the bill policy and 80% will be on the basis of the claim, then
I know that it is my real value
and at that time one should not get the surprise
that I have to pay 22%, if he did
not know then everything
is clearly mentioned in your policy, hence Gokhru or
polypropylene, it is clearly written in it that
if  Who has the payment or not, how much is their
element of all that, then it happens, let's
talk about submission, there is an increase in many things, there is an
increase in the treatment of the cutlet, that the other person will
get this much, this is
mentioned in the policy, hey, the policy has different
spiritual aspects, so definitely do that, if
you had a crime problem, do not open that
policy in your book latest,
open rate today and check what is there,
what is not, there is any torment, if
you have difficulty in understanding the terms and conditions, then
please get in touch with us today or talk to your city,
our number is just below,
we are ready to do for any clarification, if we
talk about images and students, then
you have to take care of the payment, submit the
ascendant explosion should be given
in the policy, births are
not of a limited unique pattern,
many are not in polythene, so you should do one thing
because many teams
come anyway, Manish Pal's part was
deleted to erase the politician,
when you do not have a positive attitude, the
insurance company will not give, so
what input do you have in your policy from birth, what is your birth  It
is activated and mainly there are some romantic
emotions which are not covered in the policy
like you
take intoxicants, then if there is hospitalization due to this then if you
keep it then there is no constipation, if there is
hospitalization due to participation in adventurous activities then that
also does not cause constipation, a proper
video has been made on tuition for a month, you
can go through what is accurate
in the policy, prominently advisor also there are such
things which are mentioned by consumables,
that is covered by your
policy, due to which your toiletries, your
registration and star charges are not covered,
they have not been covered,
donor screening charges, if there is a window or
transplant then donor screening
charges are not covered in this role
because
you will find it in your entire policy document,
please go through it, it has been secret, it is mysterious
to know what is active voice
and motivated, if you know this then you will
not suffer from any problem, cat me and
rendering and 20 so accident cycle this  The thing
I will tell you is that your left will never go
bad, so they will not say that
I did not get the medicine, so that you will
not be confused, whatever you have got,
explain what you need to know so that
drinking the mixture can make the smooth medicine mysterious,
your inclusion of policy in this
period policy, Tabla Mirch and health, if you
know what is there in your policy, we will
set it accordingly with your infections and deficiencies,
and if you know these things seriously, it is
not certain that someone is telling you about skin treatment, but let me tell you and
self-respect is the key, that the
horoscope present in the encounter is you have, whenever MS Word,
if you did not know, even the doctor will not be able to do it,
if something is happening, then this
thing will help to counter it 100
times, request you to go through your policy
document
properly, read something, if you do not understand then
contact your city, if you are unable to click on our help
chart, then please get in
touch with our email ID, take an
appointment, that is the commission  Let's withdraw into giving solutions to them without
any
application. Many people who are
watching the video here know that we have
tried to solve their problems without any application, wherever we can, whatever we can do, whatever we can do, whatever we can do, whatever we can do, whatever we can do, whatever we can do,
this is the point which
you have to keep in mind so that your
insurance claim settlement can be smooth. If you
want to tell us anything from your digestion,
please share in the comment
section and if you like it, then please use the like button and if you like it, then do it right now
and don't
forget to subscribe. We will meet
you in the next video, it is on specific
[music]
that girl
do